let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which HTML tag is used to display a numbered list?",
    answer: "&ltol&gt",
    options: ["&ltul&gt", "&ltol&gt", "&ltli&gt", "&ltlist&gt"],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which CSS property is used to center text horizontally?",
    answer: "text-align",
    options: ["align", "justify-content", "text-align", "center"],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which JavaScript method displays a message box to the user?",
    answer: "alert()",
    options: ["print()", "alert()", "display()", "popup()"],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which SQL command is used to add new data into a database?",
    answer: "INSERT INTO",
    options: ["ADD DATA", "INSERT INTO", "UPDATE", "PUT"],
  },
  // {
  //   numb: 5,
  //   question: "Which HTML tag is used to insert a line break?",
  //   answer: "&ltbr&gt",
  //   options: ["&ltlb&gt", "&ltbreak&gt", "&ltbr&gt", "&ltnewline&gt"],
  // },
  // {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Which CSS property is used to set the background color?",
  //   answer: "background-color",
  //   options: ["bgcolor", "background", "background-color", "color"],
  // },
  // {
  //   numb: 7,
  //   question: "In JavaScript, which symbol is used for addition?",
  //   answer: "+",
  //   options: ["*", "-", "+", "="],
  // },
  // {
  //   numb: 8,
  //   question: "Which SQL keyword is used to remove duplicate records?",
  //   answer: "DISTINCT",
  //   options: ["DELETE", "REMOVE", "DISTINCT", "UNIQUE"],
  // },
  // {
  //   numb: 9,
  //   question:
  //     "Which HTML attribute specifies an image file in the &ltimg&gt tag?",
  //   answer: "src",
  //   options: ["alt", "src", "link", "file"],
  // },
  // {
  //   numb: 10,
  //   question: "Which CSS property changes the color of the text?",
  //   answer: "color",
  //   options: ["font-color", "color", "text-color", "font-style"],
  // },
  // {
  //   numb: 11,
  //   question: "Which JavaScript keyword is used to declare a variable?",
  //   answer: "var",
  //   options: ["variable", "v", "var", "define"],
  // },
  // {
  //   numb: 12,
  //   question: "Which SQL command deletes all data from a table?",
  //   answer: "DELETE",
  //   options: ["REMOVE", "DROP", "DELETE", "CLEAR"],
  // },
  // {
  //   numb: 13,
  //   question: "Which HTML tag is used to create a hyperlink?",
  //   answer: "&lta&gt",
  //   options: ["&ltlink&gt", "&lta&gt", "&lthref&gt", "&lturl&gt"],
  // },
  // {
  //   numb: 14,
  //   question: "Which CSS property controls the size of the text?",
  //   answer: "font-size",
  //   options: ["text-size", "font-style", "font-size", "size"],
  // },
  // {
  //   numb: 15,
  //   question: "Which JavaScript method is used to print output in the console?",
  //   answer: "console.log()",
  //   options: ["print()", "log()", "console.print()", "console.log()"],
  // },
  // {
  //   numb: 16,
  //   question: "Which SQL command is used to retrieve data from a table?",
  //   answer: "SELECT",
  //   options: ["GET", "SELECT", "READ", "SHOW"],
  // },
  // {
  //   numb: 17,
  //   question: "Which HTML element is used to display the largest heading?",
  //   answer: "&lth1&gt",
  //   options: ["&lth6&gt", "&lth1&gt", "&lthead&gt", "&ltheader&gt"],
  // },
  // {
  //   numb: 18,
  //   question: "Which CSS property adds space inside an element's border?",
  //   answer: "padding",
  //   options: ["margin", "border", "spacing", "padding"],
  // },
  // {
  //   numb: 19,
  //   question: "Which JavaScript operator is used to compare two values?",
  //   answer: "==",
  //   options: ["=", "==", "===", "!"],
  // },
  // {
  //   numb: 20,
  //   question: "Which SQL keyword is used to combine two or more conditions?",
  //   answer: "AND",
  //   options: ["OR", "AND", "IF", "JOIN"],
  // },
  // {
  //   numb: 21,
  //   question: "Which HTML tag is used to insert an image?",
  //   answer: "&ltimg&gt",
  //   options: ["&ltimage&gt", "&ltimg&gt", "&ltpic&gt", "&ltphoto&gt"],
  // },
  // {
  //   numb: 22,
  //   question: "Which CSS property changes the shape of the mouse cursor?",
  //   answer: "cursor",
  //   options: ["pointer", "cursor", "hover", "icon"],
  // },
  // {
  //   numb: 23,
  //   question: "In JavaScript, what does '//' mean?",
  //   answer: "Single line comment",
  //   options: ["End of code", "Error", "Single line comment", "Break line"],
  // },
  // {
  //   numb: 24,
  //   question: "Which SQL statement is used to change data in a table?",
  //   answer: "UPDATE",
  //   options: ["ALTER", "CHANGE", "UPDATE", "MODIFY"],
  // },
  // {
  //   numb: 25,
  //   question: "Which HTML tag is used to display bold text?",
  //   answer: "&ltb&gt",
  //   options: ["&ltstrong&gt", "&ltbold&gt", "&ltb&gt", "&lttext&gt"],
  // },
];
